Why won't you get Jhaal? Pick up the phone.
See my demand. It's a simple ic38
black presentation of a hill match. Now you
tell me, importance is given to tasty. I turn cardamom into
stone.
[Music]
Whatever you have made me, there's nothing wrong in it,
but friend, helmet should be
given importance. No, I am
laughing a lot. That Devi Agarwal, when I
drove the scooter, that film Vinod Khanna, I will
not add the episode number.
What do you think if there are any issues,
Falguni, I am that friend who reminds everyone to
drive here. Sharma Nagar,
Kriya starts driving the scooter. I am the oil.
Hi Vikram Bhatt, expression of 'Now if we
forget me, then how will this work? Come on,
your boyfriend goes on a
bike trip to Ladakh with his guide friends, so he would
take me with him and along with the food, he would have given me a fruit and sweets, so
friend, tell me too, me too,
and sign this petition, so this record is broken.